coincap.io 2019-05-29

# CoinCap.io, CoinCap Apps

CoinCap.io, CoinCap Apps
Online Privacy Notice
Data protection and security are important to CoinCap ("CoinCap"; "we"), as is your trust in our
company and services. CoinCap is committed to processing your personal data responsibly and
in compliance with legal requirements.
This Online Privacy Notice describes how we collect and process your personal data when you
use our website www.coincap.io (including any sub-sites thereof; "the website") or the CoinCap
Android and iOS mobile apps (the “apps”).
Personal data we collect and process in order to make the website available
You can visit the website and obtain information about our services without telling us who you
are. As with any connection with a webserver, however, the server on which we host the
website automatically logs and temporarily stores certain technical data.
Technical data that is stored includes the IP address and operating system of your device, the
data and time of access, or the type of browser you use to access the website. This is required
for technical reasons to make the website available to you. To the extent we, thereby, process
personal data, we do so based on our legitimate interest to bring you the best possible user
experience and to safeguard the security and stability of our systems.
Our website uses fonts by Google LLC ("Google") ("Google Fonts"). To integrate Google Fonts
into the website, your browser establishes a connection to the Google server. In doing so, the IP
address of your device is transmitted to Google. Google logs records of font queries and
protects this data from unauthorized access. Google analyzes aggregated data to optimize
Google Fonts and identify which websites use Google Fonts. Further information on Google
Fonts can be found here: https://fonts.google.com. Further information on how Google handles
personal data can be found here: ​https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en​.
Personal data we collect and process to provide services to you and to respond to your
inquiries
We use services of Zendesk, Inc. ("Zendesk") to answer live queries on the website, in which
we have a legitimate interest. Zendesk uses cookies in order to provide these services. Further
information on data protection and your options in connection with the services of Zendesk can
be found here: ​https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/​ (Zendesk
Privacy Policy) and ​https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/cookie-policy/
(Zendesk Cookie Policy).

Data we collect and process to analyze and improve the use of the website; use of
cookies
In addition, based on our legitimate interest to bring you the best possible user experience, we
analyze the use of the website to gain insight on how we may improve our services. The
website uses cookies (text files that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when
you visit a website) to support this analysis.
The data we collect may include information on the type of web browser or device you use to
access the website, the geographical region where you access the website, the date and time of
your access, and the parts of the website you access.
We also use cookies to analyze the use of the website, to optimize our services and to enable
the use of marketing tools. Further information on web analysis and our marketing activities can
be found below.
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google LLC ("Google"). Google
uses cookies to collect the information that is required to evaluate your use of the website in
order to create reports on the use of the website and to provide other services that support our
analysis and improvement of the use of the website, in which we have a legitimate interest. We
use Google Analytics only with IP anonymization enabled. This means that your IP address will
be shortened beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a
Google server in the USA and shortened there. Accordingly, Google only stores the information
collected via cookies in anonymous form and processes it in aggregated form. You can prevent
Google Analytics from using your data by downloading and installing a browser add-on to
disable Google Analytics (​https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en​). Further information
on data protection and your options in connection with Google Analytics can be found here:
https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en​.
We use services of Cloudflare, Inc. ("Cloudflare") in order to identify trusted web traffic (i.e. to
identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client
basis), in which we have a legitimate interest. Cloudflare uses cookies in order to provide these
services. The cookies do not correspond to any user ID in your web application, and do not
store any personal data. Further information on data protection and your options in connection
with the services of Cloudflare can be found here: ​https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/
(Cloudflare Privacy Policy) and ​https://www.cloudflare.com/cookie-policy/​ (Cloudflare Cookie
Policy).
We use the services of Amplitude, Inc. (“Amplitude”) in order to track product usage and
investigate user reported bugs in the CoinCap Android and iOS mobile apps. Amplitude
automatically collects data about users such as IP address, device type, country and language.
Further information on data protection and your options in connection with the services of
Amplitude can be found here: ​https://amplitude.com/privacy​ (Amplitude Privacy Policy).

By adjusting your web-browser's settings accordingly, you can prevent the storage of cookies on
your device and the collection of data. Note, however, that some functions of the website may
be limited or unavailable if you disable the storing of cookies.
Data that we collect and process to target potential customers
We use Google Tag Manager to generate tags for the website and applications. These tags
enable us to tailor marketing measures for our services to potential customers (re-targeting).
We use advertising technologies by Google (AdWords). Google sets conversion cookies in
accordance with our settings in Google Tag Manager. This is necessary for checking the
effectiveness of the respective advertising campaigns. We have a legitimate interest in this. We
also use Google Tag Manager to set re-targeting tags. These tags enable us to target users
with information about our services when they visit different websites. For information regarding
your choices in relation to usage-based online advertising, see:
http://www.youronlinechoices.com​. For information about your options in connection with
cookies, see above "Data we collect and process to analyze and improve the use of the
website; use of cookies".
Access to device information or other information classified as sensitive by Google and
how we use that information
We collect Android advertisement IDs from our users, which we use to collect the device type
and specific line number of any application crashes to allow us to debug any crashes and make
a better and more useful application.
We also use Crashlytics for debugging purposes. Further information on data protection and
your options in connection with the services of Crashlytics can be found here:
https://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf​ (Crashlytics Privacy Policy)
How we process and protect your personal data; how long we store it
We collect, process and protect your personal data responsibly and in accordance with
applicable laws. We process it only for the purposes for which you provide the personal data to
us or as set forth in this Online Privacy Notice. We store your personal data only for as long as
this is necessary.
We collect and process your personal data only for the purposes for which you provide us with
these data, as set forth in this Online Privacy Notice or in accordance with applicable laws.

We apply adequate technical and organizational security measures, commensurate with the
level of known risk, in order to protect the confidentiality and integrity of the personal data we
collect on the website.
We store your personal data only for as long as this is necessary for us to fulfil the purposes for
which the data was collected, as set forth in this Online Privacy Notice, or, when applicable, as
long as we are legally required to retain the personal data.
With whom we share your personal data
In connection with the offers and services provided on the website, to protect our legitimate
interests or to fulfil legal requirements, it may be necessary to share your personal data with
business partners of CoinCap as well as with public authorities and courts.
Specifically, such sharing of data may be necessary to respond to your inquiry, to provide
access to additional information, or to follow up on your inquiry and inform you on new services
or offers following your opt-in to receive such communications.
Further, to the extent we are requested by public authorities or courts and legally required to do
so, we will share your personal data with them or other third parties.
The data sharing may include transfers to companies or organizations in countries without an
adequate standard of data protection. In these cases, we transfer personal data in accordance
with applicable provisions on the international transfer of personal data, such as, where
applicable, the respective provisions of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
The rights you have regarding your personal data
You have certain individual rights regarding the personal data that we collect and process about
you through the website.
You have the right to access or receive certain information about the personal data we process
about you. You also have a right to have your personal data rectified, to object to the processing
of your personal data, or to ask us to restrict processing or delete your personal data. If the
GDPR applies and we process your personal data to perform a contract with you or based on
your consent, you also have the right to receive a copy of your personal data for the purpose of
transferring such data to a third party.
Please note, however, that your rights are subject to exceptions or derogations. Specifically, we
may need to further process and retain your personal data to perform a contract with you or
your company or organization, to protect our legitimate interests (such as the establishment,
exercise or defense of legal claims) or to comply with legal requirements. To the extent
permitted by law, namely to protect the rights and freedoms of others or to protect our own

legitimate interests, we may therefore refuse to satisfy your request or we may satisfy your
request only restrictedly.
Lastly, you have a right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority.
Who we are and how to contact us
CoinCap is the controller in relation to the collection and processing of personal data through
the website and apps. CoinCap is owned by ShapeShift Global Limited, a corporation formed
under the laws of the United Kingdom.
If you have any questions or concerns, you may contact us through the ShapeShift Help Center,
located here: ​https://shapeshift.zendesk.com/hc/en-us​.
To inquire about the collection or processing of your personal data in connection with the
website, or if you have any questions or concerns about this Online Privacy Notice, you may
contact us via email at ​privacy@shapeshift.io​.
For all correspondence, please include any necessary identifying information such as your
name, return e-mail, and any other information relevant to your request. Failure to do so may
prevent us from providing a response.
How we can change this Online Privacy Notice
We reserve the right to change this Online Privacy Notice at any time. The version published on
the website is the applicable version.
May 2019
